gomiso.com 2011-12-29

# Privacy | Miso

## Information Collected. 

When you visit the Site, web servers collect general information about your visit (such as time, date and the address of the website from which you entered the Site), which is stored as anonymous, aggregate data. Additionally, Miso also collects more specific information about you and your use of the Service (such as demographic data, profile data and frequency or duration of use). Collecting such data ("Traffic/Usage Data") may entail the use of software programs, cookies, IP addresses or other numeric codes used to identify a computer or mobile phone. 

Miso is a service designed to help you share what you are watching and where you are watching it. We collect information you provide to us directly (such as your Twitter and Facebook username and password, what you are watching, your comments, and your location) ("User Provided Information"). 

## Use of Information. 

Miso uses Traffic/Usage Data to help diagnose problems with its web servers, administer the Site and analyze User trends and behaviors. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information, but it is used to gather broad demographic data and monitor statistics to improve the Service.

Miso uses User Provided Information to provide the Service. Such uses include, but are not limited to: logging into Twitter, logging into Facebook, sharing what you are watching with friends and other users. In addition, Miso may use User Provided Information to contact you when necessary, respond to your inquiries for additional information and provide additional information according to your preferences. We may also use the User Provided Information for the purposes described in the "Sharing of Information" section below. Sometimes User Provided Information is used to send you information about products, services and features that are available at the Site or through the Service. 

## Security. 

Information collected by Miso is stored in secure operating environments that are not made generally available to the public. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or a wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Miso cannot ensure the security of any information you provide, which you do at your own risk. Once Miso receives your transmission, it will make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on Miso's systems.

## Third Party Sites. 

The Service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet (e.g., Twitter, Facebook and Foursquare) ("Third Party Sites"), and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites are not under Miso's control. Any information you share or broadcast through the Service to Third Party Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of the Third Party Sites. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Miso is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites. The use of third party applications developed using our application programming interface ("API") are subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third party application developers. 

## IP Addresses and Cookies. 

Miso may use your IP address to administer the Site and help diagnose problems with its web servers. We use your IP address to help identify you and to gather demographic information. IP addresses are also used to provide an audit trail regarding use of the Services.

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. You may be able to set your web browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may affect your ability to access and use the Service.

## Sharing of Information. 

Personal Information including, but not limited to, your name, user name, address, email address, phone number, IP address, use information and browser information ("Personal Information") is an integral part of our business. Your Personal Information is used to allow you to interact with other users of the Site, interact with others through Third Party Sites, customizing the advertising and offers you see, improving Miso and sharing information about the Service with you. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

Provision of the Service. We may share your information with third parties in the following manners (as necessary to provide the Service): We allow you to share what you are watching and where you are watching it through Miso. Information that you submit through the Service will be available to other users of the Service. Your username and profile picture will be available to to other users and on the Internet. 

Partners. We may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our Site. We share this statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Service. 

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We anticipate that we may become affiliated with and may work closely with a variety of businesses. In certain situations, these businesses may sell items to you through the Site. In other situations, Miso may provide services jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction. In such situations, we will share your Personal Information as it is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Miso's agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Miso or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Miso goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer of Miso may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of Miso and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Miso, our employees, our users or others.

Offers and Promotions. We may provide you with offers on behalf of other businesses and partners as part of the Service. 

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

## Opt-Out. 

You may elect to avoid future communications from Miso and terminate your registration to the Service by sending an email to info@bazaarlabs.com that includes your electronic mail address; provided that Miso reserves the right to use your contact information to send you important information (such as for matters related to Miso's (or your own) legal rights).

## Non-US Users. 

YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO MISO'S PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED BY MISO IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AND IN THE UNITED STATES. UNITED STATES LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY.

## Changes. 

Miso reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time. Change notices may be communicated by postings at the Site or, in the case of users who are registered with the Service, electronic mail. In any case, you should periodically check the Privacy Policy for changes. Continued use of the Service following such notice of any change to the Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes. Information collected by the Service is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

You may correct or otherwise change your User Provided Information by contacting Miso, as provided below.

## Contact. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or your dealings at this Site, please contact Bazaar Labs at:   
Bazaar Labs   
Pier 38   
The Embarcadero   
San Francisco, CA 94107 

Attn: Privacy Policy 

Email: info@bazaarlabs.com 

**Effective Date: March 26, 2010**
